在那座山上堆了一个月
sat on that hill for a month
然后滑进了我的热水浴池
before sliding into my hot tub.
你觉得是谁处理的
Who you think has to deal with that?
我猜是你的仆人或是园丁什么的
I assume your maid or gardener or something?
是的  但还是超级不爽
Well, yeah. But it's still super-obnoxious.
我才不要把那个娃娃还给你
You're not getting that doll back.
大家都是文明市民
Citizens, citizens.
作为加州未来的州长
As the future governor of California,
能利用意识形态光谱使大家达成妥协
I pride myself on probably being able to reach compromises
这是我引以为傲的事
across the ideological spectrum.
-不如我们把娃娃一分为二吧  -什么
- What if we cut the baby in half? - What?
-为什么要这么做  -不
- Why would we do that? - No.
所以你们都觉得这是个坏主意
So you both agree that's a bad idea.
也许你们也没有那么不同
Perhaps you're not so different after all?